NWLB Files 5312
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
NWLB Files
1942
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. National War Labor Board (NWLB)
5312
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Files concerning the dispute between the Bethlehem Steel Company and the Steelworkers Organizing Committee, concerning the "Little Steel Formula."
5596245
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 27, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 11, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Steel industry and trade -- Employees -- United States.; Arbitration, Industrial -- United States.; United States. National War Labor Board (1942-1945); Bethlehem Steel Corporation.; Steel Workers Organizing Committee (U.S.)
5596245
- Bethlehem Steel v. Steel Workers Organizing Committee, Hearing on COLA Wage Adjustments, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Bethlehem Steel v. Steel Workers Organizing Committee, List of Exhibits, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Bethlehem Steel V. Steel Workers Organizing Committee, Verbatim Transcript, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Little Steel Case, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Bethlehem Steel v. Steel Workers Organizing Committee, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Little Steel Case, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Opinions and Orders re: Little Steel, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Little Steel, Materials and Exhibits, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Inland Steel v. Steelworkers Organizing Committee, Fact Finding Materials, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Inland Steel v. Steelworkers Organizing Committee, Briefs, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Inland Steel v. Steelworkers Organizing Council, Exhibits and Materials, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Steelworkers Organizing Council v. Bethlehem Steel, Fact-Finding Materials, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Exhibits regarding Inflation, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Little Steel Case Materials, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Steelworkers Organizing Council v. Republic Steel, Briefs and Transcripts, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Steelworkers Organizing Council v. Youngstown Steel Co., Materials and Exhibits, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 8)